

# CONTACT:

Phone: 09066274154

Mobile: +234906627414 Address: New Castle, Akure

Email: olamijisotomi@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS:**

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node js, Express js, Mongodb, Python, Git.
- Strong communication, leadership and teamwork skills.
- Self-motivated and able to work independently or in a team settings.
- Creative problem solver with an eye for detail.
- Collaboration
- Critical Thinking

# SOTOMI OLAMIJI O. FULLSTACK-DEVELOPER

#### SUMMARY

Experienced frontend developer with two years of expertise in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript with React framework, as well as Firebase. Currently pursuing a degree in Urban and Regional Planning at the Federal University of Technology Akure. Now a full stack developer with three years of experience using MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, React.js, and IT support, with expertise in IT security. Additionally, has one year of backend experience and is currently learning Next.js and Django.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Frontend Developer | Aipalbot USA

(October 2022 - October 2023)

- Collaborated with the development team to design and develop
- user interfaces using React is.
- Implemented responsive design and opimized the UI for various devices.
- Conducted code reviews and assisted in troubleshooting issues.

## Frontend Developer | Rangers organization

(June 2022- August2022)

- Collaborated with a team of developers to create a responsive user inerface for a real estate project.
- Utilized APIs provided by the backend developers and incoorated Sass and Material UI for styling.
- Gaining valauable knowledge and insight in the team.

# **EDUCATION**

Federal University of Technology Akure, Ondo State.

Bachelor of Science in Uban and Regional Planning(2017

-2023)

REFERENCES
Available upon request.
I hope this help! Let me know if you have any further questions or if you need anymore assistance.